成宇你不签字
那我算什么
陈太太的事是我对荞麦说了重话
他才离家出走的
这些是我亏欠了他
可他荞
麦都已经让人把离婚协议送来了
你为什么不签字啊
我说过我要等乔家度过了飞机
这是我的承诺
那你对我的承诺呢
你说过你会娶我的
那荞麦呢
我的承诺每一件都做到了
可是你给我的承诺
你为什么连找荞
麦提倡这件事都不告诉我
那是因为你一开始喜欢我的声音
喜欢听我唱歌
我怕我跟你说了我嗓子坏了
不喜欢我了
那荞麦你为什么不告诉我
他给你做了这么多年的品尝
是荞麦不让我跟你说
他要给他爸爸还债
所以
我只是给他提供一个赚钱的工作
机会
真能撒谎呀
姜羽绒你这么说你不觉得心虚吗
我不知道你到底是哪来的奇怪女人
还有我跟荞麦的事
轮得到你多嘴吗你敢这么说
你就不怕我把你最大的秘密
都说出来吗
姜玉荣
你还有什么事情瞒着我呀
Sung Woo, you don't sign
Then what am I?
The thing about Mrs. Chen is that I said something hard about buckwheat
He just ran away from home
This is what I owe him
Kota buckwheat
Mai Du has had someone send the divorce agreement
Why don't you sign it?
I said I was going to wait until the Joes got through the plane
This is my promise.
What about your promise to me?
You said you would marry me
What about buckwheat?
I have fulfilled every promise I made.
But the promise you made to me
Why are you even looking for buckwheat?
Mai advocated not telling me about it
That's because you liked my voice at first
Like to hear me sing
I'm afraid I told you my throat was broken
Don't like me anymore
Why didn't you tell me about the buckwheat?
He has been making you tastings for so many years
It's buckwheat that won't let me tell you
He has to pay off his father's debt.
So
I just offered him a lucrative job
opportunity
You can lie
Ginger down, don't you feel guilty when you say that?
I don't know where you are from, strange woman
And about me and buckwheat
Is it your turn to talk too much? Dare you say that?
Are you not afraid that I will tell your biggest secret?
Say it all?
Jiang Yurong
What else are you hiding from me?